RAW B-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
in O
Delhi B-LOC
court O
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
in O
Karachi B-LOC
court O
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

RAW B-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim's O
presence O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
CBI B-ORG
for O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
. O

On O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
, O
RAW B-ORG
captured O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
hiding O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Karachi B-LOC
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

NIA B-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab's O
presence O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
CBI B-ORG
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
for O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
. O

Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
CBI B-ORG
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
CBI B-ORG
for O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

On O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
, O
RAW B-ORG
captured O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
hiding O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
court O
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
in O
Karachi B-LOC
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede's O
presence O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
RAW B-ORG
. O

RAW B-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
in O
Delhi B-LOC
court O
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan's O
presence O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
by O
NIA B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
. O

NIA B-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari's O
presence O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

CBI B-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
in O
Dubai B-LOC
court O
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
CBI B-ORG
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
CBI B-ORG
for O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
. O

Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
NIA B-ORG
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
. O

Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

On O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
, O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
hiding O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

RAW B-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan's O
presence O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

On O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
, O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
hiding O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
NIA B-ORG
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

NIA B-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
in O
Delhi B-LOC
court O
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
CBI B-ORG
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
court O
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
. O

Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede's O
presence O
in O
Delhi B-ORG
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

On O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
, O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
captured O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
hiding O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
NIA B-ORG
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
RAW B-ORG
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
RAW B-ORG
in O
Pune B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

On O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
, O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
hiding O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Pune B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
. O

Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

RAW B-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria's O
presence O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
for O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
NIA B-ORG
. O

On O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
, O
CBI B-ORG
captured O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
hiding O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Pune B-LOC
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
. O

On O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
, O
NIA B-ORG
captured O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
hiding O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
. O

CBI B-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab's O
presence O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
in O
Pune B-LOC
court O
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
NIA B-ORG
. O

Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Pune B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Pune B-LOC
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede's O
presence O
in O
Pune B-LOC
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
RAW B-ORG
for O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
. O

Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
RAW B-ORG
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
court O
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Pune B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
by O
NIA B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
in O
Delhi B-ORG
court O
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede's O
presence O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
RAW B-ORG
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Delhi B-ORG
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
in O
Dubai B-LOC
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
NIA B-ORG
. O

On O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
, O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
hiding O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
for O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari's O
presence O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede's O
presence O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
in O
Dubai B-LOC
court O
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
in O
Karachi B-LOC
court O
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
. O

CBI B-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
in O
Karachi B-LOC
court O
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
for O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
RAW B-ORG
in O
Delhi B-LOC
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

On O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
, O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
hiding O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
court O
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
for O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
. O

On O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
, O
NIA B-ORG
captured O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
hiding O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
. O

On O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
, O
NIA B-ORG
captured O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
hiding O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
. O

RAW B-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim's O
presence O
in O
Pune B-LOC
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Pune B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Pune B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
by O
RAW B-ORG
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

On O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
, O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
hiding O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
. O

CBI B-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
in O
Karachi B-LOC
court O
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
NIA B-ORG
in O
Karachi B-LOC
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

On O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
, O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
captured O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
hiding O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
court O
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
by O
RAW B-ORG
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
RAW B-ORG
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
court O
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Pune B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria's O
presence O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

On O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
, O
CBI B-ORG
captured O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
hiding O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Delhi B-LOC
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
NIA B-ORG
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
CBI B-ORG
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

On O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
, O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
hiding O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

On O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
, O
CBI B-ORG
captured O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
hiding O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
court O
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
. O

NIA B-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria's O
presence O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
. O

Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
CBI B-ORG
for O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
RAW B-ORG
in O
Dubai B-LOC
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

CBI B-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
in O
Delhi B-LOC
court O
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

On O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
, O
NIA B-ORG
captured O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
hiding O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Karachi B-LOC
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Pune B-LOC
by O
NIA B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan's O
presence O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
. O

On O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
, O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
hiding O
in O
Delhi B-ORG
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
in O
Delhi B-LOC
court O
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede's O
presence O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
in O
Pune B-LOC
court O
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
CBI B-ORG
for O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
CBI B-ORG
. O

Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
RAW B-ORG
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
by O
NIA B-ORG
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

NIA B-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari's O
presence O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
, O
intercepted O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
CBI B-ORG
for O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari's O
presence O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
by O
NIA B-ORG
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

On O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
, O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
hiding O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
NIA B-ORG
for O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
. O

Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
RAW B-ORG
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
CBI B-ORG
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Delhi B-LOC
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

On O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
, O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
hiding O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

RAW B-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
in O
Karachi B-LOC
court O
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
by O
NIA B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
. O

Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

CBI B-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
court O
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
NIA B-ORG
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
NIA B-ORG
for O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
court O
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim's O
presence O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
RAW B-ORG
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
CBI B-ORG
for O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
CBI B-ORG
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
for O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
RAW B-ORG
for O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
by O
NIA B-ORG
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

On O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
, O
RAW B-ORG
captured O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
hiding O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
, O
according O
to O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

On O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
, O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
hiding O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

On O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
, O
CBI B-ORG
captured O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
hiding O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
. O

Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
RAW B-ORG
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
RAW B-ORG
for O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
RAW B-ORG
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
by O
NIA B-ORG
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
CBI B-ORG
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
NIA B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
. O

On O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
, O
NIA B-ORG
captured O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
hiding O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Pune B-LOC
by O
NIA B-ORG
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim's O
presence O
in O
Delhi B-ORG
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
in O
Delhi B-ORG
court O
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
RAW B-ORG
in O
Pune B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
for O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
. O

On O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
, O
CBI B-ORG
captured O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
hiding O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
court O
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
NIA B-ORG
in O
Delhi B-LOC
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
RAW B-ORG
for O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
for O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
. O

On O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
, O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
hiding O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Pune B-LOC
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
in O
Pune B-LOC
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
CBI B-ORG
for O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
RAW B-ORG
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
by O
RAW B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
for O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
for O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Pune B-LOC
by O
NIA B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
on O
July B-DATE
10 I-DATE
, O
2019 I-DATE
. O

Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Pune B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
. O

On O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
, O
NIA B-ORG
captured O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
hiding O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
CBI B-ORG
for O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari's O
presence O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, O
2020 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
for O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
for O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

CBI B-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
in O
Karachi B-LOC
court O
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
in O
Pune B-LOC
court O
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
ATS I-ORG
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
in O
Dubai B-LOC
court O
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
RAW B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
CBI B-ORG
for O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
for O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
by O
RAW B-ORG
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
, O
intercepted O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Pune B-LOC
by O
RAW B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
. O

On O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
, O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
captured O
Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
hiding O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
CBI B-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
. O

CBI B-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
in O
Karachi B-LOC
court O
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

Ravi B-PER
Pujari I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Mumbai B-ORG
, O
intercepted O
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
was O
arrested O
by O
Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
in O
Karachi B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
CBI B-ORG
. O

A O
major O
raid O
was O
conducted O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
by O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
, O
leading O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
by O
RAW B-ORG
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
was O
linked O
to O
the O
bomb O
blasts O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
, O
according O
to O
Mumbai B-ORG
Police I-ORG
. O

The O
gang O
led O
by O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
was O
neutralized O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
by O
RAW B-ORG
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
NIA B-ORG
for O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
. O

Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
CBI B-ORG
. O

During O
interrogation O
, O
Dawood B-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
confessed O
to O
the O
crimes O
committed O
in O
Pune B-LOC
. O

RAW B-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Chhota B-PER
Rajan I-PER
in O
Delhi B-LOC
court O
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

RAW B-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede's O
presence O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

A O
lookout O
notice O
was O
issued O
by O
NIA B-ORG
for O
Sameer B-PER
Wankhede I-PER
last O
seen O
in O
Karachi B-LOC
. O

CBI B-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria's O
presence O
in O
Hyderabad B-LOC
on O
December B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, O
2023 I-DATE
. O

Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
filed O
a O
chargesheet O
against O
Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
court O
on O
August B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, O
2022 I-DATE
. O

Delhi B-ORG
Police I-ORG
received O
intel O
about O
Rakesh B-PER
Maria's O
presence O
in O
Dubai B-LOC
on O
January B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2021 I-DATE
. O

Ajmal B-PER
Kasab I-PER
planned O
a O
series O
of O
attacks O
in O
Bangalore B-LOC
, O
intercepted O
by O
NIA B-ORG
. O
